Welcome. In the last lecture, we created a new input mapping context for climbing. And
欢迎。在上一节课中，我们为攀登创建了一个新的输入映射上下文。和
now we can dynamically switch to a new mapping context in runtime. And in this lecture, we
现在，我们可以在运行时动态切换到新的映射上下文。在这次演讲中，我们
look at how we can use this to achieve a two key action. So first, I'm going to close my
看看我们如何利用这一点来实现两个关键行动。所以首先，我要结束我的
project, then go back to my code. Under this climb action, I'm going to copy this one and
项目，然后返回到我的代码。在这个爬升动作下，我要复制这个
paste it in here. I'm going to call this newly created action climbHub action, and it needs
把它贴在这里。我将把这个新创建的操作命名为appbHub action，它需要
a callback function. So under this own climb action started, I'm going to create a new
回调函数。所以在这个自己开始的攀登行动下，我将创造一个新的
one. I'm going to call it own climbedHub action started and copy this one, paste it in here.
一。我将把它命名为OWN ENTERBEDHUB ACTIONAL STARTED，然后复制这个，粘贴到这里。
All right, I'm going to create a function definition and I'm going to paste the function
好的，我将创建一个函数定义并粘贴该函数
at the bottom of the CPP file. Then next thing I'm going to take care of the function binding.
在CPP文件的底部。接下来，我将处理函数绑定。
So scroll down, I'm going to copy this line for climb action, then start a new line, paste
所以向下滚动，我将复制这条线用于攀登动作，然后开始一条新的线，粘贴
it in here. I'm going to change this to climbHub action and change the callback function to
就在这里。我将把它更改为appbHub操作，并将回调函数更改为
own climbHub action started. All right, that's the coding part done. Then I'm going to go
自己的appbHub操作已开始。好了，编码部分完成了。然后我要走了
back to the callback function. I'm going to delete these t-bar functions. We don't need
返回到回调函数。我要删除这些t-bar函数。我们不需要
to see them anymore. Then I'm going to cut this one and paste it in here. So when this
再去看他们了。然后我要把这个剪下来，贴在这里。所以当这一切发生时
function is called, I'm going to print a message to the screen. So the message is going to
函数时，我将在屏幕上打印一条消息。因此，这条信息将传递给
be hopping started. And that's pretty much it. I'm going to launch my editor back. Go
开始跳跃吧。差不多就是这样。我要让我的编辑回来。去
back to my project. I'm first going to go into this actions folder. Then I'm going to
回到我的项目上来。我首先要进入这个Actions文件夹。然后我要去
select this IA climb control plus D to duplicate it. I'm going to change its name to IA_climbHub.
选择此IA爬坡控制加D复制它。我将把它的名称更改为IA_appbHub。
Then I'm going to create a key binding. So go back to this input folder, open this IMC
然后，我将创建一个密钥绑定。所以回到这个输入文件夹，打开这个IMC
climb. And in the mappings here, I'm going to click this add button to add a new action
爬上去。在这里的映射中，我将单击这个Add按钮来添加一个新操作
mapping. And in here, I'm going to select this IA_climbHub. And for the key here, I'm
映射。在这里，我将选择IA_appbHub。对于这里的关键，我是
going to click this keyboard. Then I'm going to press the space bar. So this key binding
我要点击这个键盘。然后我要按空格键。所以这个密钥绑定
here is the same as jumping. And also for this triggers here, I'm going to click this
这和跳跃是一样的。另外，对于这里的触发器，我将单击此按钮
add button to add a new element. And in the drop down here, you can see we have many options
“添加”按钮以添加新元素。在这里的下拉列表中，您可以看到我们有很多选项
we can choose. For the things we want, I'm going to select this quality action. So what
我们可以选择。对于我们想要的东西，我将选择这个质量行动。那又怎样
this means, in order to trigger the function that's bound to this key, another input action
这意味着，为了触发绑定到该键的功能，另一个输入操作
needs to be triggered as well. And in the drop down here, we can select which core action
也需要被触发。在此处的下拉列表中，我们可以选择哪个核心操作
we want. So I'm going to select this IA_climbMove. And I'm going to change this threshold to
我们想要。因此，我将选择这个IA_appbMove。我将把这个门槛改为
0.1. So now the function should only be triggered when this climb move is triggered. And just
0.1。所以现在只有当这个爬升动作被触发时，该功能才会被触发。就这样
like that, we have our two key action. Now I'm going to click save. Then I'm going to
这样，我们就有了两个关键的行动。现在我要点击保存。然后我要去
go back to my climb system character, double click to open it. And instead of the input
回到我的攀爬系统角色，双击打开它。而不是输入
here, we need to assign it the new climb hop action. So it'll be this IA_climbHop. And
在这里，我们需要为它指定新的爬升跳跃动作。所以它将是这个IA_appbHop。和
click compile. All right, let's test this. So I'm going to click play. So my key binding
单击编译。好了，让我们测试一下这个。所以我要点击播放。所以我的密钥绑定
is spacebar. I'm going to press it now. So we are jumping when we're on the ground. This
是空格键。我现在要按下它。所以当我们在地面上时，我们是在跳跃。这
is working. And I'm going to start climbing. And I'm going to try to move, then press spacebar.
正在起作用。我要开始攀登了。我要试着移动，然后按空格键。
And you can see a debug message has been printed to the screen. I'm going to try again. So
您可以看到屏幕上已经打印了一条调试消息。我要再试一次。所以
climb down, press spacebar. So the message has been printed. And if I'm not moving and
爬下来，按空格键。所以这条消息已经打印出来了。如果我不动的话
trying to press the spacebar, I can see nothing gets printed to the screen. And I'm going
尝试按空格键时，屏幕上没有打印任何内容。我要走了
to try to move to the left, press the spacebar. So the function is called. And great. Everything
要尝试向左移动，请按空格键。因此，该函数被调用。而且很棒。一切
is working as expected. So just a quick summary. In order to make this two key action work,
正在发挥预期的作用。所以，我只做一个简短的总结。为了使这两个关键行动发挥作用，
we will first need to bind the function in code. Inside of our editor, we will need to
我们首先需要在代码中绑定函数。在我们的编辑器内部，我们需要
add this new input action to our climb mapping context. And inside the mapping context, we
将这个新的输入操作添加到我们的攀登映射上下文中。在地图环境中，我们
can add triggers to define what condition should be met before this action can be triggered.
可以添加触发器以定义在触发此操作之前应满足哪些条件。
And last step, don't forget to assign new input action inside of Blueprint. Feel free
最后一步，不要忘记在Blueprint中分配新的输入操作。尽情享受吧
to refer back to the video if you need help. And I'll see you in the next lecture.
如果您需要帮助，请回看视频。我会在下一节课上见到你们。
[Music]
[音乐]